Okay I said independent, not independence, independent realtor or being on a team.
You know this is not a get rich quick business you guys and anything that's worthwhile, we all know that in life we've been taught, takes a little planning and thinking and it's about working smart and deciding what's best for you.
Okay what worked for me?
Okay at the time I got into real estate I was kind of looking at my options.
I had these children to feed.
I've got a couple of dogs.
Okay I've got this little business over here, but it's I'm kind of, you know, getting out of this business I'm in.
Do I want to run out and be an independent realtor and be my own person or do I want to be on a team?
There's a huge difference.
Let me talk about, the first thing we're going to talk about is being that independent realtor.
What an independent realtor looks like.
A) Don't put the cart before the horse.
You don't want to run out and buy yourself a little office, get the best computers, get the best coffee machines, it's about thinking in your mind, okay I'm out here.
I'm on my own in one sense.
You don't have this big broker.
This is all on me.
Sort of.
I'm an independent realtor.
Here I sit with Shelly Davis on my card as the independent realtor and I'm buying my own cards.
I'm buying my own signs and that kind of thing.
So let's talk a little bit more about that.